http://www.americandj.com/privacy-policy

Menu
ProductsLED VideoAV2X SeriesAV3X SeriesAV6XS Series Video SoftwareProcessors and ServersData Link CablesFirst Data CablesVideo Power Link CablesMain Power CablesAV3 SystemsAV6X SystemsAV4IP SeriesAV4IP SystemsDesign SeriesArkaos ProVision SeriesVision Series SystemsAutomated MoversHybrid Moving HeadsSpot Moving HeadsBeam Moving HeadsWash Moving HeadsScanner/RollersIP65 Outdoor Rated Moving HeadsIP Outdoor Rated ProductsIP65 RatedIP56 RatedIP54 RatedIPX4 RatedLighting PackagesAutomated mover packagesPar/Bar PackagesPar Can AccessoriesBattery PoweredBattery Powered Pars and BarsBattery Powered DMX TransceiverBattery Powered Gobo ProjectorsBattery Powered PinspotsBattery Powered Bubble MachinesHardware ControllerAtmosphericFazeFogHazeBubblesSnowFluid,Timer,AccessoriesLED EffectsEffectsStartec SeriesLasers EffectsStrobe EffectsPixel Controlled3D SeriesFlash Kling SeriesPixel Tube SeriesPixie Strip SeriesProjectionEllipsoidalsGobo ProjectorsSimulated Water EffectsStatic WashWifly EXR BatteryIP Rated Pars/BarsPars With ZoomCOB ParsHex ParsQuad ParsTri ParsVariable White Pars10MM ParsHex Bars10mm Bars/PanelsPar and Bar PackagesFollow SpotsPinspotsPar CansPars and BarsStatic Wash FixturesUV EffectsUV ParUV BarsUV PanelsUV Replacement BulbsControllersControl SoftwareHardware/Software/App BasedConventional Dimming ConsolesDimmer/Relay PacksHybrid/Moving Light ConsolesDMX Branch LED ControllersDimmer Control SystemsBasic ControlPower DistributionAccu CableDMX CablesSignal CablesSpeaker CablesUSB CablesAudio SignalAC ExtensionsInstrument CablesCablesIP65 Rated DMX CablesIP65 Rated Power Link CablesData CablePower Link CablesMain Power CableAccessoriesMirror BallsPar Can AccessoriesFiltersLighting StandsCablesTapeClampsRoad CasesReplacement LampsReplacement BatteriesRemotesScrimEvent FacadeAmerican AudioCasesCD PlayersHeadphonesMedia PlayersMicsMixer AccessoriesMixers (DJ)Rack EssentialsSpeaker Stands and AccessoriesSpeakersZ-Discontinued ProductsTrade ShowsInfoComm 2019NAMM 2020Nightclub & Bar 2020Houses of WorshipHalloween ProductsLDI 2019Holiday ProductsEvent LightingDance FloorsLive Stream LightingLive Stream Lighting PackagesDISCONTINUEDNew Products
News
New Product Releases ADJ Experience NewsWave Production Pros Español Events & Promotions
Contact Us
Events
Dealer Locator
Jump to Product
10 MXR
12P HEX IP
12PX HEX
12PX HEX PEARL
ArKaos 4K SERVER
ArKaos Grand VJ to XT (Upgrade)
ArKaos Grand VJ XT (License)
ArKaos Grand VJ2 (License)
ArKaos GrandVJ 2
ArKaos GrandVJ 2.0XT
ArKaos Kling Force DMX
ArKaos Kling Force LED
ArKaos LED Master (License)
ArKaos Media Master Express (License)
ArKaos Media Master Express (Upgrade from 4 to 5)
ArKaos Media Master Express Software (Backup Boxed)
ArKaos Media Master Express Software (Backup License Only)
ArKaos Media Master Express V5
ArKaos Media Master Pro (Upgrade from 4 to 5)
ArKaos Media Master Pro 5 (Backup Boxed)
ArKaos Media Master Pro 5 (Backup License)
ArKaos Media Master Pro 5 (License)
ArKaos Media Master Pro Upgrade (from Express)
ArKaos MM License Dongle
ArKaos Stadium Server
ArKaos Stage Server Express
Arkaos Stage Server Pro
ArKaos Studio Server
AV2FC
AV2RB
AV2X
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how ADJ uses and protects any information that you give ADJ when you use this website. ADJ is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. ADJ may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
American DJ collects IP address/domain name combination of users to the Web site, the electronic mail addresses of users who communicate with American DJ via electronic mail, aggregate information on pages users access or visit, user-specific information on pages users access or visit and information volunteered by users. The information American DJ collects is used for internal review and may be used to improve the content of the Web site, to customize the content and/or layout of the Web site for each individual user, or to notify user about updates to the Web site. Any communications or materials sent to the Web site by any user via electronic mail or otherwise, including any comments, data, questions, suggestions or the like, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Any use of such material does not violate any user's rights including moral rights, privacy rights, proprietary or other property rights, publicity rights, rights to credit for material or ideas, or any other right, including the right to approve the way American DJ uses such material. Any material submitted to this Web site may be adapted, broadcast, changed, copied, disclosed, licensed, performed, posted, published, sold and transmitted by American DJ anywhere in the world, in any medium. American DJ is free to use, without compensation to user, any concepts, ideas, know-how or techniques contained in any communication you send to the Web site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing and marketing products using such information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, American DJ has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information American DJ collects online. Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. American DJ cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information user transmits to American DJ or from American DJ's services. User understands that any message or information sent to the Web site may be read or intercepted by others. By submitting information to American DJ, user consents to the use of it as described above. If user does not want to be contacted by American DJ in the future, user should not submit any data to American DJ. To keep user in control of user's information and the communications directed to user, American DJ allows user to opt-out of receiving communications from American DJ. If user objects to any use of user's information by American DJ, user may send a request via electronic mail to webmaster@americandj.com or by modifying user's information on the form containing such information submitted by user online. American DJ reserves the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time and for any reason. Any changes to this Policy posted on the Web site apply as soon as they are posted. By continuing to use the Web site after any changes are posted, user acknowledges acceptance of those changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@adj.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Copyright © 2020 ADJ Products, LLC. All rights reserved.
